<div id="resume">
  <div id="version">v4.0</div>
  <!--
  <a href="about">
  <img src="/assets/QR_blog.lowkeysoftware.com_about.png" alt="QR code to about page" id="qr_code" />
  </a>
  -->

  <div class="vcard">

    <!-- Microformats! -->

    <p id="name" class="fn">Brent Haas</p>

    <div id="contact-info">
      <p> <span class="contact-detail">Location: </span>
        <span class="adr">
          <span class="locality">San Francisco,</span>
          <span class="region"> CA</span>
        </span>
      </p>
      <p><span class="contact-detail">Cell:</span> <span class="tel">408-372-7473</span></p>
      <p><span class="contact-detail">Email:</span> <a class="email" href="mailto:brenthaas+resume@gmail.com">brenthaas@gmail.com</a></p>
      <p><span class="contact-detail">Website:</span> <a class="url" href="http://lowkeytravels.com">lowkeytravels.com</a></p>
      <p><span class="contact-detail">Code:</span> <a class="url" href="https://github.com/brenthaas?tab=repositories">github.com/brenthaas</a></p>
    </div>
  </div>

  <div id="objective" class="summary">
      I am a passionate and talented Ruby developer looking to contribute my software design and development skills to an innovative team focused on user experience and strong software design principles.
  </div>

  <dl>
    <dt class="section-title">Skills</dt>
    <dd class="section">
      <div class="entry">
        <div class="entry-head">
          <span class="org">Languages and Frameworks</span>
        </div>
          <!-- make this a list and style=none it to display better -->
        <p class="wins">Ruby, Rails, RSpec, Cucumber, RabbitMQ, Capistrano, Javascript, Jasmine, Backbone Marionette, Twitter Bootstrap, Chef, Perl, Java, Python, C#, SQL, HTML, CSS, XML</p>
      </div>
      <div class="entry">
        <div class="entry-head">
          <span class="org">Technical skills</span>
        </div>
        <ul class="wins">
          <li class="win">Passion for both learning and teaching in all areas</li>
          <li class="win">Excellent collaboration and team building skills</li>
          <li class="win">Experience with massively scaled systems</li>
          <li class="win">Solid understanding of software systems and architecture</li>
        </ul>
      </div>
    </dd>

    <dt class="section-title">Experience</dt>
    <dd class="section">
      <div class="entry">
        <div class="entry-head">
          <span class="org">Yerdle</span>
          <span class="location">San Francisco</span>
          <span class="date">10/14-Present</span>
        </div>
        <div class="job_role">Server-side Rails Developer</div>
        <ul class="wins">
          <li class="win">Re-architected invoicing and credit accounting system for better security and auditing</li>
          <li class="win">Assisted with core architecture redesign and de-coupling to better adapt to business rules</li>
          <li class="win">Worked closely with mobile development team on API development</li>
        </ul>
      </div>

      <div class="entry">
        <div class="entry-head">
          <span class="org">CrowdFlower</span>
          <span class="location">San Francisco</span>
          <span class="date">02/14-08/14</span>
        </div>
        <div class="job_role">Full-Stack Web Developer in Customer Engineering</div>
        <ul class="wins">
          <li class="win">Worked as part of a small, fast paced, high performing development team</li>
          <li class="win">Developed new features for multiple Rails apps/services as part of an enterprise platform</li>
          <li class="win">Worked closely with our product manager to resolve customer issues quickly and effectively</li>
        </ul>
      </div>

      <div class="entry">
        <div class="entry-head">
          <span class="org">ThredUp</span>
          <span class="location">San Francisco</span>
          <span class="date">01/13-11/13</span>
        </div>
        <div class="job_role">Full-Stack Web Developer in Warehouse Operations</div>
        <ul class="wins">
          <li class="win">Lead developer on backbone applications used to reduce shipping and receiving errors, track defects and increase order turnaround</li>
          <li class="win">Collaborated with stakeholders to gather requirements and determine deadlines</li>
          <li class="win">Worked closely with operators to investigate defects</li>
          <li class="win">Investigated problems with, and developed solutions for architecture issues</li>
        </ul>
      </div>

      <div class="entry">
        <div class="entry-head">
          <span class="org">International Travel</span>
          <span class="location">Worldwide</span>
          <span class="date">02/10-10/12</span>
        </div>
        <div class="job_role"> Worldwide traveler volunteering on art and technical projects</div>
        <ul class="wins">
          <li class="win">Wrote travel blog covering 24 months of worldwide travel</li>
        </ul>
      </div>

      <div class="entry">
        <div class="entry-head">
          <span class="org">Yahoo!</span>
          <span class="title">Tools developer / Operations Lead</span>
          <span class="location">Sunnyvale, CA</span>
          <span class="date">06/05-02/10</span>
        </div>
        <div class="job_role"> Technical lead and tools developer for a large-scale globally distributed user database </div>
        <ul class="wins">
          <li class="win"> Designed and deployed the back-end database for Yahoo!’s Open Social services </li>
          <li class="win"> Provided 24x7 / 15 min. operational support for mission-critical database with 99.999% uptime </li>
          <li class="win"> Trainer and Technical Lead for highly skilled US and Indian operations teams </li>
        </ul>
      </div>

    <dt class="section-title">Education</dt>
    <dd class="section">
      <div class="entry">
        <div class="entry-head">
          <span class="org">University of Arizona</span>
          <span class="location">Tucson, AZ</span>
          <span class="date">June 2002</span>
        </div>
        <span class="wins">
          <p class="win">Received Bachelors of Science, Computer Science</p>
        </span>
      </div>
    </dd>

    <dt class="section-title">Accomplishments</dt>
    <dd class="section">
      <div class="entry">
        <ul class="wins">
          <li class="win">Received Yahoo! “Bustin’ Tail Pail” for Excellence in Engineering -awarded by COO</li>
          <li class="win">Nominated four times for Yahoo! Super Star Award for Excellence</li>
          <li class="win">My Art Projects:  <a href="http://flaminglotus.com" class="url">flaminglotus.com</a>  <a href="http://fluxfoundation.org/category/portfolio/">fluxfoundation.org</a>  <a href="http://aurorapaloalto.com">AuroraPaloAlto.com</a>
        </ul>
      </div>
    </dd>
  </dl>
</div>

