<div id="resume">
  <div id="version">v1.4</div>

  <img src="/assets/QR_brent-haas.com_about.png" alt="Photo of Brent" id="pic" />

  <div class="vcard">
    
    <!-- Microformats! -->
    
    <p id="name" class="fn">Brent Haas</p>
    
    <div id="contact-info">
      <p> <span class="contact-detail">Address: </span>
        <span class="adr">
          <span class="street-address">1103 Valencia St. </span>
          <span class="locality">San Francisco,</span>
          <span class="region"> CA</span>
        </span>
      </p>
      <p><span class="contact-detail">Cell:</span> <span class="tel">408-372-7473</span></p>
      <p><span class="contact-detail">Email:</span> <a class="email" href="mailto:brenthaas@gmail.com">brenthaas@gmail.com</a></p>
      <p><span class="contact-detail">Website:</span> <a class="url" href="http://www.brent-haas.com">brent-haas.com</a></p>
      <p><span class="contact-detail">Code:</span> <a class="url" href="https://github.com/loquie">github.com/loquie</a></p>
    </div>
  </div>
            
  <p id="objective" class="summary">
      I am a passionate and talented new Rails developer looking to contribute my software development and team building skills to an innovative software project focused on user experience and strong design principles. 
  </p>
    
  <dl>
    <dt class="section-title">Skills</dt>
    <dd class="section">
      <div class="entry">
        <div class="entry-head">
          <span class="org">Languages and Frameworks</span>
        </div>
          <!-- make this a list and style=none it to display better -->
        <p class="wins">Ruby, Rails, RSpec, Cucumber, Javascript, Jasmine, Perl, Java, Python, C#, SQL, HTML, CSS, XML</p>
      </div>
      <div class="entry">
        <div class="entry-head">
          <span class="org">Technical skills</span>
        </div>
        <ul class="wins">
          <li class="win">Strong understanding of full web stack and computing fundamentals</li>
          <li class="win">Passion for both learning and teaching in all areas</li>
          <li class="win">Excellent collaboration and team building skills</li>
        </ul>
      </div>
    </dd>

    <dt class="section-title">Experience</dt>
    <dd class="section">
      <div class="entry">
        <div class="entry-head">
          <span class="org">International Travel</span>
          <span class="location">Worldwide</span>
          <span class="date">02/10-05/12</span>
        </div>
        <div class="job_role"> Worldwide traveler volunteering on art and technical projects</div>
        <ul class="wins">
          <li class="win">Designed and developed small Android applications and Rails sites as personal projects</li>
          <li class="win">Wrote travel blog covering 18 months of worldwide travel</li>
          <li class="win">Assisted businesses and individuals in troubleshooting computer and network issues</li>
        </ul>
      </div>
            
      <div class="entry">
        <div class="entry-head">
          <span class="org">Yahoo!</span>
          <span class="title">Tools developer / Operations Lead</span>
          <span class="location">Sunnyvale, CA</span>
          <span class="date">06/05-02/10</span>
        </div>
        <div class="job_role"> Technical lead and tools developer for a large-scale globally distributed user database </div>
        <ul class="wins">
          <li class="win"> Developed tools to automate complex system configurations and simplify operational tasks </li>
          <li class="win"> Designed and deployed the back-end database for Yahoo!’s Open Social services </li>
          <li class="win"> Provided 24x7 / 15 min. operational support for mission-critical database with 99.999% uptime </li>
          <li class="win"> Trainer and Technical Lead for highly skilled US and Indian operations teams </li>
        </ul>
      </div>
            
      <div class="entry">
        <div class="entry-head">
          <span class="org">Hewlett-Packard Corp.</span>
          <span class="title">Support Engineer</span>
          <span class="location">Cupertino, CA</span>
          <span class="date">03/03-06/05</span>
        </div>
        <ul class="wins">
          <li class="win">Designed and developed a software tool used to parse and display XML documents (Perl) </li>
          <li class="win">Investigated and diagnosed defects in an order enterprise configuration tool and Knowledge Base </li>
          <li class="win">Worked closely with developers and customers to resolve defects quickly and accurately </li>
        </ul>
      </div> 
    </dd>
        
    <dt class="section-title">Education</dt>
    <dd class="section">
      <div class="entry">
        <div class="entry-head">
          <span class="org">In-Person Training</span>
          <span class="location">San Francisco, CA</span>
          <span class="date">05/12-12/12</span>
        </div>
        <span class="wins">
          <p class="win">
            <strong>Courses:</strong> Ruby Bootcamp, Rails Bootcamp, Mastering Backbone.js</p>
        </span>
      </div>
      <div class="entry">
        <div class="entry-head">
          <span class="org">Online Training</span>
          <span class="location">coursera.com</span>
          <span class="date">10/12-11/12</span>
        </div>
        <span class="wins">
          <p class="win"><strong>Courses:</strong> Sofware as a Service using Rails (UC Berkeley), Human Computer Interaction (Stanford)</p>
        </span>
      </div>
      <div class="entry">
        <div class="entry-head">
          <span class="org">University of Arizona</span>
          <span class="location">Tucson, AZ</span>
          <span class="date">June 2002</span>
        </div>
        <span class="wins">
          <p class="win">Received Bachelors of Science, Computer Science</p>
        </span>
      </div>
    </dd>
        
    <dt class="section-title">Professional<br /> Accomplishments</dt>
    <dd class="section">
      <div class="entry">
        <ul class="wins">
          <li class="win">Received Yahoo! “Bustin’ Tail Pail” for Excellence in Engineering -awarded by COO</li>
          <li class="win">Nominated four times for Yahoo! Super Star Award for Excellence</li>
          <li class="win">Check out the art I helped make:  <a href="http://flaminglotus.com" class="url">flaminglotus.com</a> <a href="http://fluxfoundation.org/category/portfolio/">fluxfoundation.org</a>
          <li class="win">Follow my World Travels:  <a href="http://lowkeytravels.com" class="url">lowkeytravels.com</a>
        </ul>
      </div>
    </dd>
  </dl>
</div>

